// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
const questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following statements is true about similar triangles?",
    answer: "They have the same angles",
    options: [
      "They have the same angles",
      "They have the same side lengths",
      "They have the same area"
    ],
    
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Two triangles are similar if:",
    answer: "Their corresponding side lengths are congruent",
    options: [
      "Their corresponding angles are congruent",
      "Their corresponding side lengths are congruent",
      " Both a and b"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the ratio of the lengths of the corresponding sides of two similar triangles?",
    answer: "The same for all corresponding sides",
    options: [
      "The same for all corresponding sides",
      "Different for each corresponding side",
      "The ratio is not defined"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " Which of the following is not a criterion for proving two triangles similar?",
    answer: "SAS (side-angle-side)",
    options: [
      "AA (angle-angle)",
      "SAS (side-angle-side)",
      "AAS (angle-angle-side)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If two angles of one triangle are congruent to two angles of another triangle, then the triangles are:",
    answer: "Similar",
    options: [
      "Congruent",
      "Neither congruent nor similar",
      "Similar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What two numbers if we add we get '72' and if we multiply we get '1296' ",
    answer: "36, 36",
    options: [
      "24, 24",
      "12, 12",
      "54, 54",
      "36, 36"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What two numbers if we add we get '48' and if we multiply we get '576' ",
    answer: "24, 24",
    options: [
      "56, 56",
      "14, 14",
      "32, 32",
      "24, 24"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What two numbers if we add we get '55' and if we multiply we get '750' ",
    answer: "25, 30",
    options: [
      "71, 4",
      "25, 2",
      "21, 3",
      "25, 30"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What two numbers if we add we get '36' and if we multiply we get '315' ",
    answer: "15, 21",
    options: [
      "74, 9",
      "31, 5",
      "63, 5",
      "15, 21"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is a property of similar triangles?",
    answer: "Their corresponding angles are equal",
    options: [
      "Their corresponding angles are equal",
      "Their corresponding side lengths are equal",
      "Their corresponding altitudes are equal"
    ]
  },
];
